{
  "data": [
        {
            "question": "The party had to stop because the neighbours complained that ______ music was too loud.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- Use \"the\": when you are about to make it clear which person or thing you mean ",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Michelle has three dogs and a rabbit. She doesn't like _____ cats.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- Omission of Articles: If common noun is in the form of plural noun, it will not take any",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Dan has ______ saxophone.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- A: used to show that you are referring to a general type of person or thing and not a specific person or thing",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Dan can play ______ saxophone very well.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- The: \t used to say which type of musical instrument someone plays",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "8"
        },
        {
            "question": "A man who comes from France is called ______ Frenchman.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- A:  used to show that you are referring to a general type of person or thing and not a specific person or thing\n",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "8"
        },
        {
            "question": "In most countries in the European Union people use ______ Euro.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- The + name of currency",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Today ______ black rhino is one of the most endangered species in the world.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- The: used before a singular noun when you are referring to a particular type of thing or person in a general way",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "8"
        },
        {
            "question": "One reason why ______ car is such a popular method of transport is because it is very convenient.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- The: used to refer to something that everyone knows because it is part of our natural environment or part of daily life",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "8"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the UK you have to be over the age of 17 to drive ______ car.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- A= one",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "8"
        },
        {
            "question": "______ Swiss are famous for their cheese and chocolate.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- Use \" the\": with nationality words, to mean 'the people of a particular country' ",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "8"
        }
    ]
}